<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CelebStatements>
	<Topics>
	<!--MAKE SURE NEUTRAL IS FIRST. HARD CODING-->
		<Topic name="Neutral">
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>Why are they called mannicures and not WOmanicures?</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Best. Kale. Lemongrass. Smoothie. Ever. #foodgasm</Tweet>
				<Tweet>just read about hitler. what a jerk omg #jerkface</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Yall know how i feel about japan: love it!</Tweet>
				<Tweet>@WillFerrell thats wat WHO said? #dontGetIt</Tweet>
				<Tweet>White people are in all over america! #diduknow</Tweet>
				<Tweet>if i had a dinosaur, id feed him whiskey</Tweet>
				<Tweet>wat are YOU wearin?</Tweet>
				<Tweet>always have chopsticks for dat sesame chicken #yum</Tweet>
				<Tweet>the bible has a LOT of stuff about wine!</Tweet>
				<Tweet>@bradmartinie that is so sweet! Love that stuff! #bromies4life</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Been missin my home dojo on tour</Tweet>
				<!--Tweet></Tweet>
				<Tweet></Tweet>
				<Tweet></Tweet>
				<Tweet></Tweet>
				<Tweet></Tweet-->
			</Tweets>
			<Speeches>
				<Speech>My favorite yoga mat is definitely the one with a picture of Yoda.</Speech>
				<Speech>I've just returned from a tour of the Starbucks of southeast Asia.</Speech> 
				<Speech>The trick is to eat only green food on Fridays</Speech>
				<Speech>Boys just wanna have fudge!</Speech>
				<Speech>My dog only eats gluten-free raw-hide.</Speech>
				<Speech>The Holocaust was a real tragedy. Hashtag, "never again".</Speech>
				<Speech>Panda bears are so cute. I have lots of pictures of Pandas. </Speech>
				<Speech>I really admire Sarah Palin's stance on education. Plus she's hot.</Speech>
				<Speech>Crocodiles are so cool. I would totally be a crocodile for a day.</Speech>
				<Speech>Why are people worried about climate change? Everyone has A/C these days.</Speech>
				<Speech>Like it? Totally learned it from this guy in India on a mountain.</Speech>
				<Speech>There's nothing weird about my relationship with my beautiful mother!</Speech>
			</Speeches>
		</Topic>
		
		<Topic name="Toast">		
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>LOL my hand smells like Brad's hamper #grossStuff #burntToast #lolwat</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Brie on melba toast rox my sox #foodporn #orderves</Tweet>
				<Tweet>@kylieRoseRulz The weirdest place had to be in a toaster. #realtalk</Tweet>
			</Tweets>
			<Speeches>
				<Speech>My favorite breakfast food has got to be French Toast.</Speech>
				<Speech>Just bought the cutest toaster.</Speech>
				<Speech>Let me go on record saying this to Will Smith: "You're toast bro!"</Speech>
			</Speeches>
		</Topic>
		<Topic name="Gaza">
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>Portland. Jakarta. Cairo. Gaza. Dublin. #willNOTtour</Tweet>
				<Tweet>This place is SO boring! Cant wait til this guy stops droning on about gaza #yawn </Tweet>
				<Tweet>Why cant we be friends? #cmonGaza #amirite</Tweet>
				<Tweet>ew. Ty needs to blow that zit up like its the gaza strip! #pimples #gross #worldevents</Tweet>
			</Tweets>
			<Speeches>
				<Speech>That's like a style of pubic hair right? A 'Gaza Strip'?</Speech>
				<Speech>I bet I could end the problems in Gaza if I sent everyone there an iPod.</Speech>
				<Speech>No, I'm pretty sure Gaza is a member of Wu-Tang Clan</Speech>
				<Speech>"Mo' money, mo' problems": Gaza in a nutshell</Speech>
			</Speeches>
		</Topic>
		<Topic name="German People">
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>Best smelling ppl in europe are totally the germans.</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Just found this pic of me and monica and this german dude. #thatdudewasfat</Tweet>
			</Tweets>
			<Speeches>
				<Speech>I think the worst drivers are the Germans.</Speech>
				<Speech>I just read something about Germn women and sausage...</Speech>
			</Speeches>
		</Topic>

	</Topics>
</CelebStatements>