<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CelebStatements>
	<Topics>
	<!--MAKE SURE NEUTRAL IS FIRST. HARD CODING-->
		<Topic name="Neutral">
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>Why are they called mannicures and not WOmanicures?</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Best. Kale. Lemongrass. Smoothie. Ever. #foodgasm</Tweet>
				<Tweet>just read about hitler. what a jerk omg #jerkface</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Yall know how i feel about cambodia: love it!</Tweet>				
				<Tweet>White people are in all over america! #diduknow</Tweet>
				<Tweet>if i had a dinosaur, id feed him whiskey</Tweet>
				<Tweet>wat are YOU wearin?</Tweet>
				<Tweet>always have chopsticks for dat sesame chicken #yum</Tweet>
				<Tweet>the bible has a LOT of stuff about wine!</Tweet>
				<Tweet>@bradmartinie that is so sweet! Love that stuff! #bromies4life</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Been missin my home dojo on tour</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Watching Wolf of Wall Street on my phone #lameparty #normalTuesday</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Getting sad that plaid season is ending and I have to care about what I wear. </Tweet>
				<Tweet>http://insta.pic/bGTR4j #latestintern #freakingOUT #smoothie #hoverparent</Tweet>
				<Tweet>People who shouldn't wear yoga pants: men, hippo bitches.</Tweet>
				<Tweet>.@snuckles764 You know it! #baconisworsethancigarettes</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Edward Snoden can get internet in Russia but I can't get cell service on the beach? #thanksobama</Tweet>
				<Tweet>.@frendlez I wear the watches cause I love em not cause I'm paid to ;)</Tweet>
				<Tweet>I should put my phone in a bag and tweet from my shower. #sober</Tweet>
				<Tweet>KFC billboard telling me to eat chicken is like telling @bbJesPink to smoke crack</Tweet>
				<Tweet>GOD DAMN I LOVE PEPSICLE FLSVORED GUM #sponsored</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Just texted my butler to give my champagne the #IceBucketChallenge</Tweet>
				<Tweet>I really respect Nicki Minaj as an artist and performer. #Anacondawantssome #callmemaybe </Tweet>
				<Tweet>I won't sell em for less than $5mil. </Tweet>
				<Tweet>Sorry, last one was a text, ignore #nsa</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Not saying Hitler was right. but the nigga had facial fashion. #justsaying #movember</Tweet>
			</Tweets>
			<Speeches>
				<Speech>My favorite yoga mat is definitely the one with a picture of Yoda.</Speech>
				<Speech>I've just returned from a tour of the Starbucks of southeast Asia.</Speech> 
				<Speech>The trick is to eat only green food on Fridays</Speech>
				<Speech>Boys just wanna have fudge!</Speech>
				<Speech>My dog only eats gluten-free raw-hide.</Speech>
				<Speech>The Holocaust was a real tragedy. Hashtag, "never again".</Speech>
				<Speech>Panda bears are so cute. I have lots of pictures of Pandas. </Speech>
				<Speech>I really admire Sarah Palin's stance on education. Plus she's hot.</Speech>
				<Speech>Crocodiles are so cool. I would totally be a crocodile for a day.</Speech>
				<Speech>Why are people worried about climate change? Everyone has A/C these days.</Speech>
				<Speech>Like it? Totally learned it from this guy in India on a mountain.</Speech>
				<Speech>There's nothing weird about my relationship with my beautiful mother!</Speech>
				<Speech>I think Brad Coopz is a saint</Speech>
				<Speech>… No, not since my parents kicked it</Speech>
				<Speech>Strawberry smoothie... Haven't spiked it yet. </Speech>
				<Speech>Yeah, stay in school and shit</Speech>
				<Speech>Hashtag Fuck YEAH</Speech>
				<Speech>Yeah yeah! Top scrub in da house!</Speech>
				<Speech>I'll ask my account, but I think I donated last to Mothers Against GTA or Cards Against Humanity </Speech>
				<Speech>My shoes? Lemur hide. Cashmere socks.</Speech>
				<Speech>Not ALL men look this good, she should be grateful I hit her up. </Speech>
				<Speech>I mean, I get that they’ve got seven-year olds or whatever making the Nikes… but I thought we wanted to create jobs?</Speech>
				<Speech>No, she was a massage therapist I’m pretty sure? Honestly I’m not sure how she got that video of me sleeping.</Speech>
				<Speech>Does ‘basic bitches work like the N-word? Like, only other bitches are allowed to call them that?</Speech>
				<Speech>Listen, that chick was lying! ….Whatever it is that she may or may not have accused me of maybe or maybe not doing. </Speech>
				<Speech>Okay, but just to play devil’s advocate here… no, really, they’re considering me for Al Pacino’s role in the remake.</Speech>
			</Speeches>
		</Topic>
		<Topic name="Japan">
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>just saw some japanese chick eating ice cream. HOT #yellowfever #foodporn</Tweet>
				<Tweet>yo brad just showed me some sick tentacle porn on his phone #wtfjapan #gross</Tweet>
				<Tweet>last night i dreamed i was 007 and i was with this HOT japanese chick #jamesbond #wetdream #youknow</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Does Japan made iPhones? Do I gotta burn my own phone! #yellowswine</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Shit Japan, check your water! Not a single yellow bitch here can reach my crank! #2shortshorties</Tweet>
			</Tweets>
			<Speech>
				<Speech>Did you know that all the girls in Japan actually dress like Sailor Moon to go to school every day?</Speech>
				<Speech>Did I ever tell you guys about the time I got my girl Gwen to let me borrow her Harajuku girls for a weekend?? See, we had this rooftop hotel room with like a minibar hot-tub thing, and one of the girls took so many shots she was apparently like drowning a little bit but we didn’t know it cuz she was all yelling but like in Japanese and we were all laughing and laughing...</Speech>
				<Speech>I was promoting my new album on tour in Nagasaki so I got onstage and I was all like, "This is the SECOND hottest thing an American has dropped on this town!!!"</Speech>
				<Speech>...But apparently Geisha's aren't actually prostitutes?? Anyway she was really pissed…."</Speech>
				<Speech>...and she was trying to explain it but I don’t get how international phone codes work, so I just told her that if she DID turn out to be knocked up, I wanted her to name it Hideki, and this part was really clever, because I figure Hideki Haggen-Dazs would be such a weird name that it'll show up on Google, so I set an alarm on Siri to check in 15 years. </Speech>
			</Speech>
		</Topic>
		
		<Topic name="Tweet Will Ferrell or Talk in a Jamaican Accent">
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>@WillFerrell thats wat WHO said? #dontGetIt</Tweet>
				<Tweet>@WillFerrell Dude, when are we gonna shoot that porno you've been Dark Mailing me about?</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Can't stop thinking about that time I watched Space Jam high with a cut out of @WillFerrell. </Tweet>
				<Tweet>Dude, when are we gonna shoot that porno you've been Dark Mailing me about? @WillFerrell</Tweet>
				<Tweet>@Pharrell you're @WillFerrell's brother right? Can you send me his numba, I'm dying here. </Tweet>
				<Tweet>Anyone who knows @WillFerrell, my number is 7872482437. </Tweet>
				<Tweet>"There’ll be so much more room for activities!!" lol you kno I can’t get enough a them @WillFerrell StepBrothers quotes.</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Baby don’t be like that with the blockin you know I was playin’, @WillFerrell YOU KNOW I DON’T KNOW HOW TO QUIT YOU</Tweet>
				<Tweet>DON’T BE SUCH A LITTLE BITCH @WillFerrell YOU KNOW I CAN MAKE ALT ACCOUNTS FASTER THAN YOU CAN BLOCK THEM</Tweet>
			</Tweets>
			<Speech>
				<Speech>Ja mon! I be hittin da bong loike a bobbysled in June, mon.</Speech>
				<Speech>Ja mon, I focked Her loike a goat. Flip pin' crazy, mon.</Speech>
				<Speech>Easy mon, easy mon, easy mon! Dees life ain't for dat brawl?</Speech>
				<Speech>You mon. Youuuu. Pick up dat hair inta sweetin fro mon.</Speech>
				<Speech>Yo bodmon. Yo broken my crack pipe mon. Yous be paid me for that no mon?</Speech>
				<Speech>Ey! She be hawt mon! Git out da way, mon. Come offa dat! Lemme climbondat bitch badman.</Speech>
				<Speech>My last album was hawter than a green snake under a sugar cane truck, mon!</Speech>
				
			</Speech>
		</Topic>	
		<Topic name="Gaza">
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>Portland. Jakarta. Cairo. Gaza. Dublin. #willNOTtour</Tweet>
				<Tweet>This place is SO boring! Cant wait til this guy stops droning on about gaza #yawn </Tweet>
				<Tweet>Why cant we be friends? #cmonGaza #amirite</Tweet>
				<Tweet>ew. Ty needs to blow that zit up like its the gaza strip! #pimples #gross #worldevents</Tweet>
			</Tweets>
			<Speeches>
				<Speech>That's like a style of pubic hair right? A 'Gaza Strip'?</Speech>
				<Speech>I bet I could end the problems in Gaza if I sent everyone there an iPod.</Speech>
				<Speech>No, I'm pretty sure Gaza is a member of Wu-Tang Clan</Speech>
				<Speech>"Mo' money, mo' problems": Gaza in a nutshell</Speech>
				<Speech>My latest real estate venture is this little cafe I bought on the Gaza Strip</Speech>
				<Speech>My latest album just dropped like a rocket on the Gaza Strip, yo!</Speech>
			</Speeches>
		</Topic>
		<Topic name="German People">
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>Best smelling ppl in europe are totally the germans.</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Just found this pic of me and monica and this german dude. #thatdudewasfat</Tweet>
			</Tweets>
			<Speeches>
				<Speech>I think the worst drivers are the Germans.</Speech>
				<Speech>I just read something about Germn women and sausage...</Speech>
			</Speeches>
		</Topic>
			<Topic name="Toast">		
			<Tweets>
				<Tweet>LOL my hand smells like Brad's hamper #grossStuff #burntToast #lolwat</Tweet>
				<Tweet>Brie on melba toast rox my sox #foodporn #orderves</Tweet>
				<Tweet>@kylieRoseRulz The weirdest place had to be in a toaster. #realtalk</Tweet>
			</Tweets>
			<Speeches>
				<Speech>My favorite breakfast food has got to be French Toast.</Speech>
				<Speech>Just bought the cutest toaster.</Speech>
				<Speech>Let me go on record saying this to Will Smith: "You're toast bro!"</Speech>
			</Speeches>
		</Topic>

	</Topics>
</CelebStatements>